sanmar.com 2019-03-10

# Privacy Policy | SanMar

SanMar Corporation promises to protect the personal information given to us by our customers, website visitors and information included in our mailing lists.

#### COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

SanMar collects personal data that you voluntarily provide to us. This might include your name, the name of your business, your address, phone number, e-mail address and other similar information that we need to provide services to our customers. We also analyze our website logs to constantly improve the value of our website to our visitors. This includes page views, unique views, unique visitors, repeat visitors, frequency of visits, and peak volume traffic periods. In our use of this service we do not gather, request, record, require, collect, or track any internet users' personally identifiable information. Additionally, we may gather personal information from you if you apply for employment with SanMar. Unless required by law, SanMar retains personal information only for as long as necessary to allow us to accomplish the purposes for which we collect it.

#### USE OF COOKIES

Cookies are small data files that are downloaded onto your computer when you visit our site that automatically identify your browser to our server whenever you interact with our site. We link the cookies to your personally identifiable information on our servers but no personal information is stored in the cookies themselves. We use cookies to track your use of our site and to authenticate users when signing in. We do not share cookies with any other site. You may deactivate cookies in your browser at any time if you do not want to use cookies. Cookies are not required to visit SanMar.com.

#### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

SanMar does not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease personal information shared to our representatives, collected on our website or included in our email lists to any third party. We will only use the personal information that you provide for the reason that you provided it to SanMar. For example, if you provide us with a shipping address we may use that personal information to create a shipping label. We may also share certain personal information with vendors or service providers that SanMar uses to service its customers. For example, a shipping address may be shared with the carrier used to deliver the package to you. SanMar may also share your personal information with vendors that help us provide you with services and help us provide you with an excellent customer experience. SanMar’s third party vendors only have access to your personal data for a short period of time. SanMar makes best efforts to be sure that its vendors are contractually obligated to carefully handle data received from SanMar and to delete it after a reasonable period of time.

#### INFORMATION UPDATES AND OPTING OUT

Information updates to your account or changes to your personal information will be made at your request. SanMar makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that all data, including your personal information, is accurate. You may unsubscribe from SanMar's promotional and marketing e-mail lists at any time. Unsubscribe links are provided in all promotional and marketing e-mails. You may also unsubscribe by calling Customer Service Toll Free at (800) 426-6399, emailing us at [sales@sanmar.com](mailto:sales@sanmar.com) or by writing us at E-Mail Privacy Policy Team c/o Customer Service, SanMar Corporation, 22833 SE Black Nugget Rd., Suite 130, Issaquah, WA 98029. You may also use these contacts to close your account at any time. Please note that personal information may be retained after you close your account to allow us to meet our obligations to you, resolve problems and meet applicable legal requirements.

#### DATA SECURITY

We take precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.

#### GDPR RIGHTS

European Union data subjects have certain rights related to personal information under the EU General Data Protection Regulation. If you qualify, it is your right to request (a) access to your personal information; (b) data correction to your personal information is incorrect or incomplete; (c) object to SanMar’s use of your personal information because there is a strong legitimate reason that we should not process your personal information that is unique to you; or (d) SanMar’s deletion of your personal information. If you provided us with consent related to your personal data, you can withdraw that consent at any time. You may also unsubscribe from promotional and marketing e-mails at any time by contacting SanMar.

#### DATA SECURITY

We take precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. Please note that our data security precautions are not a guarantee that that data will not be subject to unauthorized access, disclosure or destruction if our safety precautions are breached. Electronic disclosure of personal information may not always be secure or error free and SanMar is not responsible for disclosures that happen due to transmission errors or unauthorized interception of electronic communication. We may reach out to you electronically if we discover a data security breach. Sharing personal information with us or using SanMar.com is your agreement that we can contact you electronically to share information related to privacy and information on data security so that you can take steps to protect your information. You may also be entitled to receive written notice of a security breach under your local law.

#### ENFORCEMENT

If for any reason you believe that SanMar has not adhered to these privacy principles or you wish to object to or withdraw previously provided consent to process your personal information, please notify us by e-mail at [customertechsupport@sanmar.com](mailto:customertechsupport@sanmar.com) and we will endeavor to review and promptly correct the problem. Please use the words 'Privacy Policy' in the subject line.

#### EXTERNAL LINKS

This website provides links to various websites that SanMar does not control. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred out of our website and connected to the website of the organization or company that you selected. Even if an affiliation exists between our website and a third party website, we exercise no control over linked sites. Each of these linked sites maintains its own independent privacy and data collection practices and procedures. If you visit a website that is linked to our site, you should consult that site's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

#### INTERNATIONAL INFORMATION TRANSFERS

Any personally identifiable information that you provide to SanMar will be collected directly on servers located in the United States and maintained on servers located in the United States. If you are located outside the United States, this means that any information you provide will be transferred abroad. While SanMar is committed to providing your information with the highest level of privacy protection, we believe you should know that the general level of protection for personal information in the United States may not be the same as that provided in other countries, including those that belong to the European Economic Area.

#### TERMS AND MODIFICATIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY

By using this website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our privacy policy. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not disclose any personal information through this site. SanMar may modify this privacy policy at any time at its discretion and modifications are effective upon being posted on this site. You are responsible for reviewing this privacy policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on the SanMar website, please contact us at [customertechsupport@sanmar.com](mailto:customertechsupport@sanmar.com). If you wish to speak to SanMar’s Data Protection Officer, please contact:

Name: Paul Harvey   
Title: Senior Manager, Information Technology Infrastructure Services   
Phone: 800.346.3369 ext.5688   
E-mail: [paulharvey@sanmar.com](mailto:paulharvey@sanmar.com)

This policy was last updated on May 25, 2018
